<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Moyo-From the depth</name>
	<author>Nemonian</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.2</li>
		<li>1.3</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>Nemonian.MY</packageId>
	<description>
Moyo-From the depth
	
A strange-humanlike figure with tail and pale blue skin rise from the beach, the Moyos have arrived to the surface.
The descendants of a glitterworld wanderlusts, who saw the depth of the ocean an ideal place for habitation.
Years and years of modification, so long that they have forgotten their origins now recides in the depth of the rimworld, Striving in their arcology called the 'lighthouse'.
	
Recently, Moyos have discovered a particular substance from their body. Named 'Deep blue', it originates form the constand modifications their ancesters had.
This made a massive impact on thier society. Having many opportunities in medical purposes, some Moyos saw it as an opprtunity for a fortune - Maybe you too.
	
Перевод Moyo-From the depth. Перевод кривой и не полный. Но рабочий и сделан под HSK версию Мойо. Для Мойо из бездны есть хороший перевод в мастерской. Для правки перевода обращайтесь в дискорд ко мне С̷и̷л̷ь̷ф̷#6762
	
== Race ==
- generally slower: includes global work speed, movement speed, lower melee dodge chance, but has an added benefit of slower hunger rate.
- but sturdy: has a bonus in base health and has lower flammability, Though they are a bit heavier than average human.
- higher psychic sensitivity: lurking in the depths could have an effect, or is it cause of so much ultrasound being used?
- excels in medical and drugs: they will do thoes jobs faster and better. due to their society or memories of body modification engraved in their DNA.
	
- produces Deepblue: their blood can be refined to be injected to other races, improving their pysiche but making them dependent to it. Also can be used to make varieties of drugs which can be used by everyone. It will be a great asset for your colony.
- there are ways to get more: process their corpse, or optain other option through research.
	
	
== Contents ==
*apparels are race-restricted but they can wear any apparel for the sake of compatability.
-16 weapons
-15 apparels + 7 royal tagged apparels (more to be added)
-40 backstories (more to be added)
	
-1 production building (workbenches could be added to avoid clutter of recipe menu)
-4 drugs and 1 medicine made with deepblue (more to be added)
	
-custom scenario and a faction
	
== Special thanks to ==
-gquake 꾸악 https://steamcommunity.com/id/gguake/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100 : providing code crucial to the mod.
-Gouda quiche https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561197992216829/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100 : providing code crucial to the mod(MoHar hediffs).
-all the great people in RimWorld Korea discord server.
-all the great people in rimworld alien races discord server.
	</description>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
			<displayName>HumanoidAlienRaces</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>goudaquiche.MoharFramework</packageId>
			<displayName>MoHAR framework</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2057001924</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</li>
		<li>goudaquiche.MoharFramework</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>
